[{"answer": " So, I have to tell you this funny thing I heard on the radio today", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Sure.  What was it", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 13, "question": " So, I have to tell you this funny thing I heard on the radio today", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " The DJs had this contest where listeners called in to the show.  While the DJ", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Sure.  What was it", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": "What?  Did people actually do that?  They baby talked on the radio?  Did thei", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 19, "question": " The DJs had this contest where listeners called in to the show.  While the DJ", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, the first guy that called in tried to call his girlfriend, but his mom answere", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 23, "question": "What?  Did people actually do that?  They baby talked on the radio?  Did thei", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " What did she do", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Well, the first guy that called in tried to call his girlfriend, but his mom answere", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Nothing.  She just talked to him like it was a normal conversation.  Since sh", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 28, "question": " What did she do", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " Crazy", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 35, "question": " Nothing.  She just talked to him like it was a normal conversation.  Since sh", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I know.  It was so funny.  The DJs were cracking up", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Crazy", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " I bet.  Did someone win the prize", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 37, "question": " I know.  It was so funny.  The DJs were cracking up", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Yeah.  The next guy that called in phoned his girlfriend and she answered.  H", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I bet.  Did someone win the prize", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " She must have been so embarrassed once she found out what was going on", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Yeah.  The next guy that called in phoned his girlfriend and she answered.  H", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Oh, she was.  She was saying, Im going to kill my boyfriend when I get home", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 43, "question": " She must have been so embarrassed once she found out what was going on", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Did they at least win something good for the prize", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Oh, she was.  She was saying, Im going to kill my boyfriend when I get home", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " I think they won concert tickets, I cant really remember", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Did they at least win something good for the prize", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " I guess it was worth it then", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 46, "question": " I think they won concert tickets, I cant really remember", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Yeah.  It was so funny.  So, do you and your husband baby talk to each other", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 47, "question": " I guess it was worth it then", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Well, I hate to admit it, but sometimes.  We have pretty cheesy nicknames fo", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Yeah.  It was so funny.  So, do you and your husband baby talk to each other", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Really?  What are they", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 52, "question": " Well, I hate to admit it, but sometimes.  We have pretty cheesy nicknames fo", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Dont tell anyone, but he calls me honey bear and I call him sweety-pie.  W", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Really?  What are they", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " That is so cute", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Dont tell anyone, but he calls me honey bear and I call him sweety-pie.  W", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": "I cant believe I just told you.  Do you and your boyfriend baby talk to each other", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 58, "question": " That is so cute", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": "Not really.  I tried to baby talk to him once and he didnt really baby talk back.  I", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 59, "question": "I cant believe I just told you.  Do you and your boyfriend baby talk to each other", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Did he baby talk back to you", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Not really.  I tried to baby talk to him once and he didnt really baby talk back.  I", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": "  No, not at all.  I just said, nothing, and kept on talking.  I think hes too mach", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Did he baby talk back to you", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " Do you think hed do it if he could get free concert tickets to his favorite band", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 69, "question": "  No, not at all.  I just said, nothing, and kept on talking.  I think hes too mach", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Maybe.  He just might do it then", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 70, "question": " Do you think hed do it if he could get free concert tickets to his favorite band", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": "Next time that contest is on the radio, you should call in and try it", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Maybe.  He just might do it then", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " That would be so funny.  Hed think I was crazy", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Next time that contest is on the radio, you should call in and try it", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " Maybe after youve dated a little longer hell be more comfortable with the bab", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 76, "question": " That would be so funny.  Hed think I was crazy", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " Maybe.  Well see.  I doubt it though", "docId": "07-09", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Maybe after youve dated a little longer hell be more comfortable with the bab", "qSentId": 79}]
